var questions = [ {
    question: 'Wermo',
    answer: 'A stupid person',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Ee chee wa maa!',
    answer: 'Gee whiz',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Kna Naa',
    answer: 'Spirit tree',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Jeerota',
    answer: 'Friend',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Kreeth',
    answer: 'Cave',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Mookiee',
    answer: 'Female baby Ewok',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Nuv',
    answer: 'Love',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Ooba',
    answer: 'Sweet',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Powa',
    answer: 'Power',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Roda',
    answer: 'To eat',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Sheeu',
    answer: 'Name',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Shetai',
    answer: 'Warrior',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Sku',
    answer: 'Hello',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Sleesh',
    answer: 'Berry',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Sunee',
    answer: 'Sun',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Teeha',
    answer: 'Thank you',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Teeket',
    answer: 'Heart',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Sut',
    answer: 'Soon',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Thek',
    answer: 'Here',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Thees',
    answer: 'Good',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'T\'hesh',
    answer: 'Quiet',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Thuk',
    answer: 'Rock',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Treek',
    answer: 'Go',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Treekthin',
    answer: 'Hourney',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Tu',
    answer: 'The',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Weewa',
    answer: 'House',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Yeha',
    answer: 'Goodbye',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Yehan',
    answer: 'Peace',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Yesh',
    answer: 'Correct',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Drin',
    answer: 'Sick',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Churi',
    answer: 'Mountain',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Dutak',
    answer: 'Arrow',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Eleeo',
    answer: 'Never',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 },
  {
    question: 'Ehda',
    answer: 'Evil',
    mValue: 1,
    __v: 0 } ];
//
// for(question in questions) {
// 	console.log("this ran ", question)
// 	var newQuestion = new Questions();
// 	newQuestion.question = questions[question].question;
// 	newQuestion.answer = questions[question].answer;
// 	newQuestion.mValue = 1;
// 	newQuestion.save().then(function(question) {console.log("question saved", question)})
// }
